"Oh, Shelly?
"A man's here
to take you away to the future!
(Sheldon:)Be sure to pack
clean underwear."
(Penny:)Okay, okay, let's try
that last line again,
(Penny:)and this time,
maybe try choking up
(Penny:)a little.
Why?
(Penny:)Well, you're losing your son.
(Sheldon:)Yes, but he's going
to a better place
(Sheldon:)where he won't get beat up...
so much.
(Penny:)All right, come on,
just try it my way.
(Penny:)Pretend you're sad
to see him go.
(Penny:)I'm gonna lead you in.
"His unique genius
is our best hope
(Penny:)for bringing peace
to a vast and troubled galaxy."
(Penny:)- That's your cue.
- I'm sorry. I just love that line.
(Sheldon:)Even the way you do it.
(Penny:)All right, come on, come on.
(Penny:)Put some real emotion into it.
(Penny:)Blah-blah, blah, blah...
"vast and troubled galaxy."
(Sheldon:)Go.
Hmm.
"Oh, Shelly?
(Sheldon:)A man's here
to take you away to the future""
"Be sure to pack clean
underwear."
(Penny:)That's good. That's good.
That's good.